Tell us what the Canary Mission is.
Well, it's a very massive program that's been going on for years and years.
It's secretly run out of Israel, and the purpose is to blacklist and dox students,
professors, and largely anybody that disagrees largely with Israel or is pro-Palestinian.
And many, many people suddenly wake up and they find out people are calling them and saying,
your name is on a blacklist, the Canary Mission blacklist.
And, you know, it's designed to intimidate these people, to get them to stop joining pro-Palestinian
groups or to stop being activists and to comply with whatever the people behind Canary Mission
wants.
And that's basically to silence them.
And the threat is that if you don't be silent, then, you know, your name's going to go on
the blacklist, and if you go look for a job when you get out of—when you graduate or
if you're trying to rise up in the professional ranks or a professorship, it's going to be
blocked because your name's on this list, and it's almost impossible to get off the list.
So that's just one of the many ways that the Israeli government has been pushing the American
public, basically, to steer away from pro-Palestinian activism.